Dylan Shaw

dylanjshaw000@gmail.com | (508) 944-1304 | New York City NY

LINKS

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/dylan-j-shaw
- https://iamdylan.surge.sh/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am passionate about transforming business initiatives into modern web solutions. My experience in technical consultative roles (Black Crow AI, Tealium) and as a developer at an ultra-fast-paced e-Comm shop (BVA) have together taught me to carefully balance client needs with business constraints. I'm comfortable working with all standard web technologies and all flavors of JS. Check out https://iamdylan.surge.sh/ for a more colorful summary.

WORK HISTORY

Black Crow AI. New York City, New York

Technical Integration Engineer | 01/2022 - Current

- Front-end maintenance of our core product: a machine learning model that delivers (client-side) a 1-10 propensity score, which denotes a user's likelihood to purchase, to be consumed inside platforms like Facebook Ads, Google Ads and TikTok, Snapchat, etc..
- Provide technical support to clients and internal stakeholders at all
 phases of the sales cycle, with emphasis on pre- and intra-demo
 phases.
- Write ad hoc JS integrations for clients to leverage propensity scores inside unsupported platforms.
- Developed a bot using Facebook Ads API to automatically build Facebook audiences in client ad accounts.
- Regularly conduct experiments to improve product efficacy (e.g., model/score accuracy, user match rate inside target platforms).

BVA. San Diego, CA
Front-end Developer | 05/2019 - 03/2020

- Built Shopify sites and in-site components for various D2C e-commerce brands including Red Bull, Good American, Pit Viper, Freshly Picked, and BioClarity.
- Co-authored a new store boilerplate theme using Slate + GraphQL +

SKILLS

- Technologies/Applications:
 JavaScript (ES5-7, TypeScript,
 vueJS, reactJS, NodeJS,
 ExpressJS, NextJS), HTML,
 CSS, SASS/SCSS, Liquid,
 Gatsby, web APIs, SQL,
 Looker, Datadog, Firebase,
 Zendesk, TealiumIQ, Shopify,
 Words With Friends
- Ecosystems: e-Commerce, digital marketing/advertising, machine learning, web analytics, stock derivatives
- Technical writing & speaking
- Product & brand advocacy
- Client retention & relationship building
- Workflow optimization & internal tooling

EDUCATION

University of San Diego San Diego, CA 2016

Bachelor of Science: Behavioral Neuroscience & Philosophy Academic Advisor, Delta Tau Delta fraternity, Theta Zeta chapter

Dev Bootcamp

San Diego, CA 12/2016

Web Development Course

VueJS + SCSS.

• Regularly held agile team meetings with designers, contract developers, project managers and client representatives.

Tealium. San Diego, CA Solutions Engineer | 05/2016 - 05/2019

- Wrote custom JS integrations for clients leveraging analytics and advertising tags from partners including Google, Omniture/Adobe, Facebook, Reddit, and Yahoo.
- Co-authored Customer Success tribal knowledge base to document workarounds for bugs in partner tags.
- Wrote extensions of TealiumIQ core library as needed for client use-cases.
- Developed a UI layer on top of TealiumIQ to automate internal processes.
- Hosted live tutorials to train clients on how to best leverage Tealium products to achieve their business goals.
- Developed Zendesk app to automatically re-assign projects of out-ofoffice teammates.